Guide to the Don Gale KSL editorial video collection 1938-2010 1978-1997
Multimedia Archives, J. Willard Marriott Library, University of Utah
- KSL editorials, 1978-1998; 2010
  - KSL editorials, 1984 May-1984 June; DVD (Disc 36)
    - Utah's special representatives, 1984 May 28 (Video 28)
    - Girl scout cookie success, 1984 May 29 (Video 29)
    - Bonuses demand performance, 1984 May 30 (Video 30)
    - Libraries begin with books, 1984 May 31 (Video 31)
    - Davis County highway link, 1984 June 1 (Video 32)
    - Wilderness compromise eases logjam, 1984 June 2 (Video 33)
    - Americans like to read, 1984 June 3 (Video 34)
    - Plan old mill development, 1984 June 4 (Video 35)
    - Medical malpractice protection needed, 1984 June 5 (Video 36)
    - Improve freeway traffic flow, 1984 June 6 (Video 37)
    - Freedom of the press day, 1984 June 7 (Video 38)
    - Arch L. Madsen, doctor of laws, 1984 June 8 (Video 39)
    - Congressional reality and deficit, 1984 June 9 (Video 40)
    - English as the official language, 1984 June 10 (Video 41)
    - Investigate wildlife division firing, 1984 June 11 (Video 42)
    - Another point of view - Carolyn McNil, re electric power rates, 1984 June 12 (Video 43)
    - Improve maintenance safety practices, 1984 June 13 (Video 44)
    - Reorganize division of corrections, 1984 June 14 (Video 45)
    - Kennecott challenges the unions, 1984 June 15 (Video 46)
    - Donald Duck has a birthday, 1984 June 16 (Video 47)
    - Father's Day, 1984 June 17 (Video 48)
    - School superintendents become targets, 1984 June 18 (Video 49)
    - Another point of view - Jeff Sermon, re credit cards, 1984 June 19 (Video 50)
    - Retain the volunteer spirit, 1984 June 20 (Video 51)
    - A tip for tourist hospitality, 1984 June 21 (Video 52)
    - Defensive driving in Utah, 1984 June 22 (Video 53)
    - So you own a corner lot, 1984 June 23 (Video 54)
    - Goodbye, eagle gate apartments, 1984 June 24 (Video 55)
    - Forget hotel at the university, 1984 June 25 (Video 56)
    - Another point of view - Craig Robertson, 1984 June 26 (Video 57)
    - Guilt by registration?, 1984 June 27 (Video 58)
    - Magic of modern dentistry, 1984 June 28 (Video 59)
    - Amtrak on the wrong track, 1984 June 29 (Video 60)
    - Utah business activity recovers, 1984 June 30 (Video 61)
  - KSL editorials, 1984 July-1984 August; DVD (Disc 37)
    - Press responds to its critics, 1984 July 1 (Video 1)
    - Preparation time for national guard, 1984 July 2 (Video 2)
    - Interest rates and the deficit, 1984 July 3 (Video 3)
    - Independence Day, 1984 July 4 (Video 4)
    - Political campaigns are disgraceful, 1984 July 5 (Video 5)
    - Warfare for tax revenues, 1984 July 6 (Video 6)
    - Threat of toxic chemicals, 1984 July 7 (Video 7)
    - Approve American Conservation corps, 1984 July 8 (Video 8)
    - Who's kidding whom?, 1984 July 9 (Video 9)
    - Hooray for cleanup program, 1984 July 10 (Video 10)
    - Discrimination in the workplace, 1984 July 11 (Video 11)
    - The new broadcast house, 1984 July 12 (Video 12)
    - Utah's billion-dollar bonus, 1984 July 13 (Video 13)
    - Politics more than elections, 1984 July 14 (Video 14)
    - The reality of foreign competition, 1984 July 15 (Video 15)
    - Civic clubs need women, 1984 July 16 (Video 16)
    - Careful of get-rich-quick schemes, 1984 July 17 (Video 17)
    - The illusion of state lotteries, 1984 July 18 (Video 18)
    - Understanding the deficit, 1984 July 19 (Video 19)
    - Applaud civilian volunteer groups, 1984 July 20 (Video 20)
    - Postal workers won't strike, 1984 July 21 (Video 21)
    - Eliminate the unitary tax, 1984 July 22 (Video 22)
    - The myth of amateur olympics, 1984 July 23 (Video 23)
    - The pioneer spirit, 1984 July 24 (Video 24)
    - Emigration canyon denied again, 1984 July 25 (Video 25)
    - Troubles at the stock market, 1984 July 26 (Video 26)
    - The Miss America debacle, 1984 July 27 (Video 27)
    - Folly of mass transit, 1984 July 28 (Video 28)
    - Buckle up... or else, 1984 July 29 (Video 29)
    - When baseball was king, 1984 July 30 (Video 30)
    - Statue of liberty syndrome, 1984 July 31 (Video 31)
    - United State: a debtor nation, 1984 August 1 (Video 32)
    - Burr trail road inevitable, 1984 August 2 (Video 33)
    - What's in a name?, 1984 August 3 (Video 34)
    - The rule of law, 1984 August 4 (Video 35)
    - Politics and public policy, 1984 August 5 (Video 36)
    - Prenatal awareness week, 1984 August 6 (Video 37)
    - Beautification or confusion?, 1984 August 7 (Video 38)
    - Get the lead out!, 1984 August 8 (Video 39)
    - The baby boom matures, 1984 August 9 (Video 40)
    - Honesty and the deficit, 1984 August 10 (Video 41)
    - Remedy for health care costs, 1984 August 11 (Video 42)
    - Lake problems not over, 1984 August 12 (Video 43)
    - The joys of yard work, 1984 August 13 (Video 44)
    - Another point of view - Grant Williams, re non-resident tuition, 1984 August 14 (Video 45)
    - Board of education candidates, 1984 August 15 (Video 46)
    - Control over arts festivals, 1984 August 16 (Video 47)
    - Summer of the hoppers, 1984 August 17 (Video 48)
    - Press compounds the problem, 1984 August 18 (Video 49)
    - Inventor of the dissector tube, 1984 August 19 (Video 50)
    - Duries in a democracy, 1984 August 20 (Video 51)
    - Week of the bow hunt, 1984 August 21 (Video 52)
    - Little Dell Dam approved, 1984 August 22 (Video 53)
    - Education's vital role, 1984 August 23 (Video 54)
    - New uses for convention facility, 1984 August 24 (Video 55)
    - Problems on the farm, 1984 August 25 (Video 56)
    - Tax laws foolish, illogical, 1984 August 26 (Video 57)
    - Business practices and courtesy, 1984 August 27 (Video 58)
    - Another point of view - Mark Hafeman, re mass transit, 1984 August 28 (Video 59)
    - Emigration Canyon comes up again, 1984 August 29 (Video 60)
    - Examine land value tax, 1984 August 30 (Video 61)
    - Football season begins, 1984 August 31 (Video 62)
  - KSL editorials, 1984 September-1984 October; DVD (Disc 38)
    - Those ubiquitous opinion polls, 1984 September 1 (Video 1)
    - Welcome, american legion, 1984 September 2 (Video 2)
    - Labor Day, 1984 September 3 (Video 3)
    - Another point of view - Camille Haney, re credit card surcharges, 1984 September 4 (Video 4)
    - School board action mistaken, 1984 September 5 (Video 5)
    - The wet, wet summer, 1984 September 6 (Video 6)
    - Prison security needs review, 1984 September 7 (Video 7)
    - Why the tax code grows, 1984 September 8 (Video 8)
    - The negative side of development, 1984 September 9 (Video 9)
    - Education and raffles don't mix, 1984 September 10 (Video 10)
    - Another point of view - Brian Melaney, 1984 September 11 (Video 11)
    - Property taxes shock taxpayers, 1984 September 12 (Video 12)
    - Back to school time, 1984 September 13 (Video 13)
    - Left lane should be open, 1984 September 14 (Video 14)
    - Bridges may need second try, 1984 September 15 (Video 15)
    - Hidden growth in government, 1984 September 16 (Video 16)
    - Transit planners at it again, 1984 September 17 (Video 17)
    - Birthday for symphony hall, 1984 September 18 (Video 18)
    - Bicycle riders not exceptions, 1984 September 19 (Video 19)
    - Do you wonder why...?, 1984 September 20 (Video 20)
    - Bankruptcy needs another look, 1984 September 21 (Video 21)
    - Actions and reactions, 1984 September 22 (Video 22)
    - End of the cold war?, 1984 September 23 (Video 23)
    - Highway patrol deserves thanks, 1984 September 24 (Video 24)
    - Those annoying phone calls, 1984 September 25 (Video 25)
    - Legislature creates own problems, 1984 September 26 (Video 26)
    - Rewrite the tax laws, 1984 September 27 (Video 27)
    - Best wishes to Don Thomas, 1984 September 28 (Video 28)
    - The "record" is no record, 1984 September 29 (Video 29)
    - Can we stamp out illiteracy?, 1984 September 30 (Video 30)
    - Free speech restrictions abhorrent, 1984 October 1 (Video 31)
    - Another point of view - Pat Sheya, re Emigration Canyon annexation, 1984 October 2 (Video 32)
    - Improve emergency number 911, 1984 October 3 (Video 33)
    - The world and its similarities, 1984 October 4 (Video 34)
    - Utah ballot proposals, 1984 October 5 (Video 35)
    - Millions of pen pals, 1984 October 6 (Video 36)
    - Can't erase credit rating, 1984 October 7 (Video 37)
    - Proposition one - uniform tax, 1984 October 8 (Video 38)
    - Tobacco companies fool youngsters, 1984 October 9 (Video 39)
    - Proposition two - annual sessions, 1984 October 10 (Video 40)
    - Sergeant York weapon a turkey, 1984 October 11 (Video 41)
    - Columbus talks to America, 1984 October 12 (Video 42)
    - Congress does it again, 1984 October 13 (Video 43)
    - Appreciating traffic controls, 1984 October 14 (Video 44)
    - Proposition three - judicial article, 1984 October 15 (Video 45)
    - Community council want parks, 1984 October 16 (Video 46)
    - Proposition four - school lands, 1984 October 17 (Video 47)
    - Paying for state conventions, 1984 October 18 (Video 48)
    - Deer hunting and education, 1984 October 19 (Video 49)
    - Tax load not unreasonable, 1984 October 20 (Video 50)
    - Discriminatory airline prices, 1984 October 21 (Video 51)
    - Proposition five- right to arms, 1984 October 22 (Video 52)
    - Another point of view - Senator Haven Barlow, re proposition 3, 1984 October 23 (Video 53)
    - Maintain runaway truck lane, 1984 October 24 (Video 54)
    - Another point of view - Ron Smith, re uniform tax (proposition 1), 1984 October 25 (Video 55)
    - Another point of view - Erv Skousen, re school lands (prop. 4), 1984 October 26 (Video 56)
    - The debates are over, 1984 October 27 (Video 57)
    - Autumn memories, 1984 October 28 (Video 58)
    - Trauma of teenage suicide, 1984 October 29 (Video 59)
    - Make it a safe Halloween, 1984 October 30 (Video 60)
    - Modernize steel mills, 1984 October 31 (Video 61)
  - KSL editorials, 1984 November-1984 December; DVD (Disc 39)
    - Another point of view - Bob Templeton, re proposition five, 1984 November 1 (Video 1)
    - Another point of view - Pamela Turner, 1984 November 2 (Video 2)
    - Warning from mother nature, 1984 November 3 (Video 3)
    - Initiative 'a' and rebuttal (cable tv programming) - Jay Lloyd and Jim Bunnell, 1984 November 4 (Video 4)
    - Your vote is needed, 1984 November 5 (Video 5)
    - Motorcycle accidents on the rise, 1984 November 6 (Video 6)
    - Another point of view - Sherm Smith, re CPA education, 1984 November 7 (Video 7)
    - City problem is a warning, 1984 November 8 (Video 8)
    - Approve year-round fishing, 1984 November 9 (Video 9)
    - Focus on the debt, 1984 November 10 (Video 10)
    - The tragedy of hunger, 1984 November 11 (Video 11)
    - Veteran's Day, 1984 November 12 (Video 12)
    - National education week, 1984 November 13 (Video 13)
    - "As american as apple pie", 1984 November 14 (Video 14)
    - Sandy City plans ahead, 1984 November 15 (Video 15)
    - BYU deserves thanks, 1984 November 16 (Video 16)
    - Toxic waste technology fails, 1984 November 17 (Video 17)
    - Small investment, large rewards, 1984 September 18 (Video 18)
    - Salt Lake food bank, 1984 November 19 (Video 19)
    - Truth about exit polls, 1984 November 20 (Video 20)
    - Don't limit terms in Congress, 1984 November 21 (Video 21)
    - Thanksgiving, 1984 November 22 (Video 22)
    - Dealing with junk mail, 1984 November 23 (Video 23)
    - Go slow on directional lights, 1984 November 24 (Video 24)
    - Peace institute now reality, 1984 November 25 (Video 25)
    - Concerns about politics, 1984 November 26 (Video 26)
    - Utility moratorium and rates, 1984 November 27 (Video 27)
    - Congratulations, Senator Garn, 1984 November 28 (Video 28)
    - Goodbye, Center Theatre, 1984 November 29 (Video 29)
    - An age of overstatement, 1984 November 30 (Video 30)
    - Keeping up with the news, 1984 December 1 (Video 31)
    - The necessities of life, 1984 December 2 (Video 32)
    - Time for museum hopping, 1984 December 3 (Video 33)
    - Resolve Emigration Canyon dispute, 1984 December 4 (Video 34)
    - Change Pentagon shopping habits, 1984 December 5 (Video 35)
    - Revise city zoning laws, 1984 December 6 (Video 36)
    - Equal time and fairness, 1984 December 7 (Video 37)
    - Rumor often misleads, 1984 December 8 (Video 38)
    - Foreign students in America, 1984 December 9 (Video 39)
    - Build the community first, 1984 December 10 (Video 40)
    - A reasoned look at pornography, 1984 December 11 (Video 41)
    - Don't drink the water, 1984 December 12 (Video 42)
    - Contradiction in the courts, 1984 December 13 (Video 43)
    - Feed the hungry day, 1984 December 14 (Video 44)
    - Your stake in the deficit, 1984 December 15 (Video 45)
    - Relief for health costs, 1984 December 16 (Video 46)
    - Quarters for Christmas, 1984 December 17 (Video 47)
    - The spirit of Christmas, 1984 December 18 (Video 48)
    - Unitary tax is not wise, 1984 October 19 (Video 49)
    - Tax load not unreasonable, 1984 December 20 (Video 50)
    - The shortest day, 1984 December 21 (Video 51)
    - The shortest day, 1984 December 22 (Video 52)
    - Academic standards for athletes, 1984 December 23 (Video 53)
    - Christmas Eve, 1984 December 24 (Video 54)
    - Christmas Day, 1984 December 25 (Video 55)
    - Support prosecutors advisory council, 1984 December 26 (Video 56)
    - Central America - overview, 1984 December 27 (Video 57)
    - Central America - Mexico, 1984 December 28 (Video 58)
    - No time for phone deregulation, 1984 December 29 (Video 59)
    - Terrorism won't stop terrorism, 1984 December 30 (Video 60)
    - Year-end thank you, 1984 December 31 (Video 61)
  - KSL editorials, 1985 January-1985 February; DVD (Disc 40)
    - New Year's Day, 1985 January 1 (Video 1)
    - Another point of view - Alden Tueller, re fund-raising by mail, 1985 January 2 (Video 2)
    - Central America - El Salvador, 1985 January 3 (Video 3)
    - Abuse of the elderly, 1985 January 4 (Video 4)
    - Power of positive thinking, 1985 January 5 (Video 5)
    - BYU: champions in many ways, 1985 January 6 (Video 6)
    - Thanks to the Mathesons, 1985 January 7 (Video 7)
    - Welcome, Governor Bangerter, 1985 January 8 (Video 8)
    - Central America - Honduras, 1985 January 9 (Video 9)
    - Decline of civilization?, 1985 January 10 (Video 10)
    - Central America - Cuba, 1985 January 11 (Video 11)
    - Sad story of drug use, 1985 January 12 (Video 12)
    - Welcome, Dr. John Bennion, 1985 January 13 (Video 13)
    - Utility tax is a symptom, 1985 January 14 (Video 14)
    - When security turns to tyranny, 1985 January 15 (Video 15)
    - Lake is a long-term problem, 1985 January 16 (Video 16)
    - The resources of government, 1985 January 17 (Video 17)
    - Central America - economics, 1985 January 18 (Video 18)
    - It's super bowl time, 1985 January 19 (Video 19)
    - Clear off the snow, 1985 January 20 (Video 20)
    - Tax benefit bill not needed, 1985 January 21 (Video 21)
    - Another point of view - Earl Vanfleet, re health care, 1985 January 22 (Video 22)
    - Thanks for good neighbors, 1985 January 23 (Video 23)
    - Mail service: a complex issue, 1985 January 24 (Video 24)
    - Better plan for the lake, 1985 January 25 (Video 25)
    - Increase cigarette tax, 1985 January 26 (Video 26)
    - Vigilante talk disturbing, 1985 January 27 (Video 27)
    - Central America - Nicaragua, 1985 January 28 (Video 28)
    - Indians badly served, 1985 January 29 (Video 29)
    - Central America - U.S. policy, 1985 January 30 (Video 30)
    - Correct block 57 mistakes, 1985 January 31 (Video 31)
    - Judges deserve better pay, 1985 February 1 (Video 32)
    - Truck regulations need revision, 1985 February 2 (Video 33)
    - Stop rent control early, 1985 February 3 (Video 34)
    - Iron County development plan, 1985 February 4 (Video 35)
    - Another point of view - Dee Hansen, re pumping the lake, 1985 February 5 (Video 36)
    - Value of the 55-mile limit, 1985 February 6 (Video 37)
    - Limit medical malpractice suits, 1985 February 7 (Video 38)
    - February is scout month, 1985 February 8 (Video 39)
    - Trillion dollar budget, 1985 February 9 (Video 40)
    - Don't reduce school age, 1985 February 10 (Video 41)
    - Children's Medical Center radiothon, 1985 February 11 (Video 42)
    - Another point of view - Dale Hawkins, re water level of lake, 1985 February 12 (Video 43)
    - Dance building high priority, 1985 February 13 (Video 44)
    - Support clear creek project, 1985 February 14 (Video 45)
    - Black History Month, 1985 February 15 (Video 46)
    - Deficit out of control, 1985 February 16 (Video 47)
    - Some programs need cuts, 1985 February 17 (Video 48)
    - Trucking regulation needed, 1985 February 18 (Video 49)
    - Case of the potted robins, 1985 February 19 (Video 50)
    - CBS buy-out plan ill-conceived, 1985 February 20 (Video 51)
    - Protect national guard property, 1985 February 21 (Video 52)
    - Utah needs veterans park, 1985 February 22 (Video 53)
    - Father of the R.O.T.C., 1985 February 23 (Video 54)
    - Income taxes down in '83, 1985 February 24 (Video 55)
    - U.H.P. - job well done, 1985 February 25 (Video 56)
    - Fishing license fees increase, 1985 February 26 (Video 57)
    - NCAA needs a conscience, 1985 February 27 (Video 58)
    - Best wishes to Mark Littman, 1985 February 28 (Video 59)
  - KSL editorials, 1985 March-1985 April; DVD (Disc 41)
    - Trouble at the mall, 1985 March 1 (Video 1)
    - Utah and the winter olympics, 1985 March 2 (Video 2)
    - Lights make a difference, 1985 March 3 (Video 3)
    - West High on the move, 1985 March 4 (Video 4)
    - Control military spending, 1985 March 5 (Video 5)
    - Highways need attention, 1985 March 6 (Video 6)
    - Davis County investment program, 1985 March 7 (Video 7)
    - City housing problem serious, 1985 March 8 (Video 8)
    - Senator Garn on hold, 1985 March 9 (Video 9)
    - Supreme court asks for help, 1985 March 10 (Video 10)
    - Reactive shade tree council, 1985 March 11 (Video 11)
    - Another point of view - Joseph Stumph, 1985 March 12 (Video 12)
    - Don't misjudge micaragua, 1985 March 13 (Video 13)
    - Support special olympics, 1985 March 14 (Video 14)
    - County complex vote set, 1985 March 15 (Video 15)
    - Freedom of information day, 1985 March 16 (Video 16)
    - The luck o' the Irish, 1985 March 17 (Video 17)
    - Theater alive and well in Utah, 1985 March 18 (Video 18)
    - Poverty on the increase, 1985 March 19 (Video 19)
    - Spring is on its way, 1985 March 20 (Video 20)
    - Property tax not equal, 1985 March 21 (Video 21)
    - ABC takeover may be beginning, 1985 March 22 (Video 22)
    - What about the 'MX'?, 1985 March 23 (Video 23)
    - Farm crisis in perspective, 1985 March 24 (Video 24)
    - The press under attack, 1985 March 25 (Video 25)
    - Another point of view - Lee Allen, re property taxes, 1985 March 26 (Video 26)
    - Time for wheel alignment, 1985 March 27 (Video 27)
    - Amtrak and its subsidy, 1985 March 28 (Video 28)
    - Utahns support the Jazz, 1985 March 29 (Video 29)
    - Highway funds hijacked, 1985 March 30 (Video 30)
    - Social security and the debt, 1985 March 31 (Video 31)
    - Lessons from the refugees, 1985 April 1 (Video 32)
    - Another point of view - Carl Buck, 1985 April 2 (Video 33)
    - Install West Valley sidewalks, 1985 April 3 (Video 34)
    - Another point of view - Dave Allred, re Utah Jazz, 1985 April 4 (Video 35)
    - Voter turnout embarassing, 1985 April 5 (Video 36)
    - South Africa needs change, 1985 April 6 (Video 37)
    - Easter Sunday, 1985 April 7 (Video 38)
    - Murder indicates value difference, 1985 April 8 (Video 39)
    - Campaign targets drunken drivers, 1985 April 9 (Video 40)
    - Afghan people need help, 1985 April 10 (Video 41)
    - Senator Hatch offers advice, 1985 April 11 (Video 42)
    - Polio is a bad memory, 1985 April 12 (Video 43)
    - End bickering over escape, 1985 April 13 (Video 44)
    - More about the Goetz case, 1985 April 14 (Video 45)
    - The tax man cometh, 1985 April 15 (Video 46)
    - Another point of view - Larry Anderson, 1985 April 16 (Video 47)
    - National library week, 1985 April 17 (Video 48)
    - Strong dollar or weak world?, 1985 April 18 (Video 49)
    - Sad comment on TV programs, 1985 April 19 (Video 50)
    - Study "star wars" concept, 1985 April 20 (Video 51)
    - Courting Utah students, 1985 April 21 (Video 52)
    - Organ donor awareness week, 1985 April 22 (Video 53)
    - Warning about AM stereo, 1985 April 23 (Video 54)
    - Hurry back, Jay Lloyd, 1985 April 24 (Video 55)
    - Enforce handicapped parking rules, 1985 April 25 (Video 56)
    - Promises for the handicapped, 1985 April 26 (Video 57)
    - It's a small world, 1985 April 27 (Video 58)
    - Raise drivers license age, 1985 April 28 (Video 59)
    - Private property week, 1985 April 29 (Video 60)
    - Studying the urban forest, 1985 April 30 (Video 61)
  - KSL editorials, 1985 May-1985 June; DVD (Disc 42)
    - Lake level research needed, 1985 May 1 (Video 1)
    - How do you explain...?, 1985 May 2 (Video 2)
    - Television: a force for good, 1985 May 3 (Video 3)
    - Solving indoor air pollution, 1985 May 4 (Video 4)
    - The buck stops..., 1985 May 5 (Video 5)
    - The people and the statue, 1985 May 6 (Video 6)
    - Arch Madsen retires, 1985 May 7 (Video 7)
    - From the Vietnam Memorial, 1985 May 8 (Video 8)
    - Press at best and worst, 1985 May 9 (Video 9)
    - Spring clean-up, trim-up, 1985 May 10 (Video 10)
    - Need for economic understanding, 1985 May 11 (Video 11)
    - Mother's Day, 1985 May 12 (Video 12)
    - Justice and altered testimony, 1985 May 13 (Video 13)
    - Another point of view - Congressman James Hansen, 1985 May 14 (Video 14)
    - Good neighbors and sharp saws, 1985 May 15 (Video 15)
    - Public servants and the public, 1985 May 16 (Video 16)
    - Honor in the Congress?, 1985 May 17 (Video 17)
    - Christopher Columbus, 1985 May 18 (Video 18)
    - National Tourism Week, 1985 May 19 (Video 19)
    - Public works week, 1985 May 20 (Video 20)
    - Another point of view - Jim Bennardo, 1985 May 21 (Video 21)
    - Nicaragua embargo mistaken, 1985 May 22 (Video 22)
    - Operation graduation, 1985 May 23 (Video 23)
    - Graduation time, 1985 May 24 (Video 24)
    - Welcome, KUED, to teletext, 1985 May 25 (Video 25)
    - Drug abuse and independence, 1985 May 26 (Video 26)
    - Memorial Day, 1985 May 27 (Video 27)
    - Grasshopper control needs cooperation, 1985 May 28 (Video 28)
    - Utah symphony board changes, 1985 May 29 (Video 29)
    - A tax increase that quacks, 1985 May 30 (Video 30)
    - County street light update, 1985 May 31 (Video 31)
    - Children's Miracle Network, 1985 June 1 (Video 32)
    - What's in a name?, 1985 June 2 (Video 33)
    - Defense companies betray trust, 1985 June 3 (Video 34)
    - Plates advise "ski Utah", 1985 June 4 (Video 35)
    - Winter olympics a good idea, 1985 June 5 (Video 36)
    - Fasten your seat belts, 1985 June 6 (Video 37)
    - Freedom of the press day, 1985 June 7 (Video 38)
    - Water shortage easy to solve, 1985 June 8 (Video 39)
    - Spy net tests system, 1985 June 9 (Video 40)
    - Don't give up on tax reform, 1985 June 10 (Video 41)
    - When boundaries disappear, 1985 June 11 (Video 42)
    - The magic of chocolate, 1985 June 12 (Video 43)
    - Takeovers pose problems, 1985 June 13 (Video 44)
    - Dogs will be dogs, 1985 June 14 (Video 45)
    - SALT treaty is a curiousity, 1985 June 15 (Video 46)
    - Fathers Day, 1985 June 16 (Video 47)
    - Trivia in the desert, 1985 June 17 (Video 48)